I get very self-aware at the airport. I
always want to make sure that I'm doing
everything right. And it's not because
I'm afraid they're going to think I'm
like up to high jinks. Hijinks is what I
call terrorism.
It's not that. I just want I want to get
through security very efficiently. Like
I want to be the best one. You ever feel
that way? Like it's a test and you
really want to kill it, right? You want
the TSA people to be kind of like
impressed with you.
It's not enough for them to know that
I'm not a threat. I want them to like be
proud of me
and like me as a person.
Every time the last TSA guy clears me, I
always want to turn back and be like,
"Okay, so what could I be doing better?"
Um, no liquids over 3.4 ounces. Laptop
was where it was supposed to be. I don't
know if you saw, I was helping with the
bins, even though it's not mandatory.
I took my shoes off in the Uber on the
way here for 40 minutes. I've been
wearing shoes. That's
I came prepared.
He's just like, "All right, kid. I'm
just going to give it to you straight.
I've been working this job day in day
out for 38 years, and I have never seen
anyone move through this line with the
grace and dignity that you displayed
here today. You're the best I've ever
seen.
The best I've ever seen." And it's not
just that.
Watching the way you handle yourself. I
saw the bins.
I just get the sense that you have
something that a lot of people that come
through this terminal don't have. A good
heart. You got a good heart, kid.
[Music]
Anyway, my name is Robert. I kind of run
things around here
and I'll be watching your career very
closely.
Thank you for reminding me why I do what
I do. He's still talking with his wife
about me over dinner. Honey, he was just
so intentional and precise
with every single one of his movements.
I've never seen anything like it.
I just hope he chooses to fly through
LaGuardia again.
Uh I do come from an immigrant family.
parents came here from Iran. And I'm
very proud of my heritage now, but when
I was a kid, I was embarrassed by it.
You know, I just wanted to fit in. I
wanted to be American. So, I distanced
myself from my culture whenever I could.
You know, my friends would come over and
be like, "Your house smells funny." Or,
"Your mom talks funny." And I'd have to
be like, "Hey, I know. What's your
problem?" Right? I was just thinking the
same. I'm just as upset as you, if not
more so. There's really no excuse for
that kind of behavior. Remember when she
called the Super Bowl the Super Bowl? I
don't care what happens to her. I don't
I don't
[Applause]
I code switch on them. You're And you're
right. These people come here
smelling like cinnamon and snakes.
I'll tell you what we Americans smell
like is amber waves of grain.
It's a It's a really weird way to grow
up because your folks depend on you way
sooner than an American family because
English was my mom's third language and
my dad's fourth, which made me like the
English professor
of the house. I had to translate
everything, you know, which is a lot of
power for a little kid to have. I would
just be like playing with my toys. I'm
seven. They walk up to me with like a
letter about our mortgage.
They're
just like, "Please, professor, can you
please decode these strange
shapes? They have no meaning to us."
I'm just like, "One moment, please.
I have nearly finished with my research
on Batman versus Ninja Turtles." You
see?
Oh my god, they're foreclosing on us.
That's crazy.
A lot of roles like that were reversed
where I would be teaching them, you
know, bedtime stories. I did all the
reading and I had to explain a lot
cuz immigrants are stupid. I don't know
if you know.
Or just be like, "Yeah, so the wolf
wants to blow their houses down so he
can eat all the pigs." That's what he
What's that, Mom?
I don't know why he doesn't just use his
paws. That's a really good question.
Maybe if we keep reading, they'll tell
us. Let's Let's keep read. That's good
active listening. Let's keep reading.
That's really good.
That's really what Yes, I remember.
There was a wolf in your town that ate a
few people. I remember it. I remember
it.
Yes, I remember. They made him the
mayor. Okay, let's get back to the
That's a Persian bedtime story. There
was a wolf in the village who killed two
children, but everybody loved him.
Find the lesson in that one.
Uh, I live with my girlfriend now. She
speaks English really well. Uh,
we've been going out for 2 years. It's
been great. She's loved my life. Uh,
she's also the reason why I'm a fat
little [__] in front of you this
evening. I've gained about 30 lbs since
we started going out. I really think the
worst thing that a woman could do for a
man is to love and accept him for who he
is.
Don't do it, ladies. He's going to take
his foot off the gas. It's
It's not a good idea. Her love is
literally killing me.
I don't think it's all her fault. I I I
do think it's just the times that we're
living in. It's too easy to eat like
crap. Now, it's crazy that I could take
out my phone right now and press a few
buttons and then in 20 minutes a man
will show up with a pizza and he legally
has to give me that pizza. That's a
disaster.
There should be a law where if the Door
Dash guy doesn't think that you should
have it, he doesn't have to give it to
you.
Just like please sir for you I don't
think it's good. Please please dond do
sir is sir is not dond do
just an exhausted Bengali man who's
trying to save my life.
I think they're Bengali. I'm honestly
not sure
but I think that's okay. I think it's
better not to know. This is an
interesting thing that I've noticed
about identifying someone's race. Like
if you say, "Oh, I can't tell the
difference between Chinese, Japanese,
Korean people. They all look the same to
me." You sound super racist. You do.
But if you say you can tell the
difference,
that's like way more racist, right?
That's like way worse. If you're like,
"Yeah, yeah, I know who's who." Head
circumference, forehead shape. Line them
up. I'll tell you. This was my grandpa's
job during the war. I'll tell you
exactly who's who.
That's way worse.
We have a dog. With with dogs, it's
completely different. Everyone knows
what every breed is. They can identify.
We can know what their personalities
are. We know even what their issues are.
And it's fine. I think the way we talk
about dogs is a little bit racist. Can
you imagine? If we spoke about
ethnicities the way we do about dogs,
you just see someone across the street
and you're like, "Oh my god, is that
Normenian?" Is that I have always wanted
one. Do you know they're so adorable?
They They're vivacious, right? They have
a joy of life. I'll tell you what you
have to watch out for, though. They have
vision problems when they get older. Did
you know that?
>> They do. My aunt had one. They do. They
have vision problems.
I get jealous of animals, man. I really
do because they don't have any
schedules. And I think that's amazing. I
feel so overscheduled. Every moment of
my life is so regimented. All of us are
right in the city especially. Every day
I have to like wake up, walk the dog,
got to stop at the pharmacy for my
girlfriend. I got to do some work. I got
It never ends. Do you know what the
schedule was for every bird in the world
today? You know what it said? It said
one thing. Chill, baby.
Be a bird.
A bird's life isn't regimented. It's
like improvisational jazz. You don't
know where it's going to go.
Eat a worm over here. Zaba, take a poop
over there. Za, a taxi killed my son.
Sure
your kids are dying all the time, but
that's jazz, baby. That's jazz.
No, we're having a really good time. Uh,
my girlfriend and I I've never lived
with anyone before and it's so much fun.
Every every night we like cuddle up on
the couch. We're watching TV. You know,
we like to watch the reality competition
shows. That's our favorite thing to
watch. And I hadn't seen these shows in
forever cuz I was single. You're not
allowed. You got to be in a couple to
watch the thing.
And they've gotten insane. Masletov,
answer it. Don't answer it. Leave it.
Masletov.
Anyway,
these shows have gotten in crazy. Like
25 years ago, a reality show is like,
listen, it's 30 people on an island.
Last one standing gets a million
dollars. That's the show. That's it. Now
it's gotten so complicated. It's like a
100 singles, 20 horses, four abandoned
cruise ships, a witch.
Whoever gets voted into the Verizon
Wireless Secret Bake Off
presented by Pepsi Wireless
before they're kidnapped by the Masked
King wins $8,000.
The prizes are they've gotten very low.
The prizes have gotten very low.
And your host, well, the movie industry
is dead. So, we managed to get
three-time Academy Award winner Meryill
Street.
Wild.
I'm uh it's my birthday in a couple of
months. Thank you so much. That was
nice.
I don't know. You probably won't see me,
so thank you.
Uh and it always makes me think
about my life, like where I'm at. And
I'm really happy with where I'm at. I
am. I I don't have any regrets. I have
one I have one regret for my whole life.
I was 6 years old. Okay. And I was
flying. I think it was my first time
flying. I was with my mom. And the
flight attendant walks up to us and she
says, "The captain would like to know if
you want to come up to the cockpit and
sit with him." They used to do this.
This was before the high jinks of 9/11.
Okay.
They used to do this. She said, "Do you
want to come into the cockpit? You can
ask questions about the aircraft. He'll
give you a little pin like he has." So
cool, right? And I didn't do it. I was
too shy.
And I regret that so much. I regret that
every day because I'll never get that
chance again. As long as I live, that's
over. I'm not seeing cockpits now in my
third. Imagine me mid-flight
calling over a flight attendant like,
"Hey,
tell a captain I want to go see the
cockpit
and uh I'm going to have some questions
about the aircraft.
I don't want a little pin like he has.
They're just like, "All right, well,
we're going to land the plane
immediately,
and once we do, your life is really
going to change fast."
They're taking me through the airport in
handcuffs. Someone yells out, "Hey, you
leave him alone." I'm like, "Robert."
He says, "You get your hands off him.
He's got a good heart."
Thanks, guys. Guys, I'm Milan Elon.
>> I'm actually I'm skipping a family party
to be here. Little baddy alert.
Happy birthday, Dad. Um
I'm done with family parties. I'm sorry.
After the last one, I decided no more.
I'm not going to do it anymore. I just
won't. Um because you ever go to a
family party and it's got the exact
opposite energy of what a party should
be, right? The the last one I went to,
my stepmom saw me coming down the
driveway with a bottle of wine and she
ran out and intercepted me and was like,
"This is actually going to be a dry
party." And I was like, "What the [__]
What the actual [__] alcohol is what
makes it the party.
You know what I mean? And then she was
like, "Well, Uncle Wayne is sober now,
so we can't drink around him anymore."
And I was like, "Oh, that's actually
pretty [__] selfish, don't you
think?" I was addicted to drugs. I would
never say to you, "Don't bring heroin to
my birthday party."
Bring it.
I want you to bring heroin to my
birthday party. Every year people are
like, "What should we bring to the
party?" And I'm dropping hints like, "I
don't know. Whatever you think's a good
time."
That's how addiction works. You know,
you always want to be around it. And um
I don't know. Sometimes people um say to
me like, "Oh, that's crazy. Like that
you were wrapped up in drugs. Like how
did that all happen?" You know, and I
always say like I was a very depressed
kid, right? like I did not see the
possibility of life and I didn't feel
like I could do anything. And believe it
or not, it's drugs that broke me of that
thought process. And I'll never forget
the day it happened. I was smoking crack
with a prostitute in a closet
and she threw up into a shopping bag.
Right. And that's standard stuff. Okay.
But but then she hung that shopping bag
up on a hanger in the closet and it hit
me like a ton of bricks. I was like, "Oh
my god, we can do whatever we want.
There's almost nothing we can't do."
And then she tried to have sex with me
like an hour later and I was like,
"Okay, not that. You are disgusting.
Sometimes people don't like that joke
cuz it sounds like I'm being antisex
work. You know what I mean? And I have
to try to remember like a lot of
people's daughters are probably on Only
Fans now. So that hits close to home.
You know what I mean? Isn't that great?
All these girls rolling around on their
mattress and their bikinis being like,
"I'm a sex worker." And it's like, "No,
no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. You got to taste a dick to be a
sex worker.
I'm sorry. I spend a lot of time with
these girls and you're co-opting
somebody else's existence,
somebody else's experience. That's
[__] up. Um I don't know.
Uh I'm uh I'm clean now. Um
All right. Yeah. I didn't think you were
going to clap for that. I almost thought
you wished I was dead. Um
I'm clean. I got a job. Um, I'm a
participating member of society. Um,
it's not my dream job. I'm a waitress,
you know what I mean? Um, but I'm using
my time as a waitress to kind of like
try to mentor these younger kids, right?
Like kind of like try to show them the
way. Um, it's not easy. I know every
generation of adult says this, you guys,
but this time I mean it. These kids are
so fresh. They're out of control. Um, I
said to this 17-year-old bus boy, I was
like, "Hey, could you do me a favor?
Could you clear that table over there?"
And he turned around to me and he was
like, "You know what? Why don't you suck
it?"
Yeah. He said that. And I was like, "You
want to know something? I would, but
you're a minor and that's illegal."
Yeah. You're not going to catch me
tripping.
I'm following all the laws now. Okay.
cuz you know I'd be like
and he put it on Snapchat and the cops
would have it like that, right guys? My
life would be over immediately. You
can't do it anymore. The golden age of
[__] kids was like 10 years ago.
Today the technology moves too quickly.
I don't know who needs to hear that in
this room, but statistically like eight
people. How crazy is that?
There are eight pedophiles in this room
and I'm going to spend the rest of my
time up here trying to figure out who it
is.
And if you're not laughing,
yeah. Yeah, just kidding. Sorry. Um,
one of my co-workers is uh pregnant and
um yeah, but she's one of those girls
that's always getting pregnant and
announcing it right away, but then she
parties so she loses the baby like a
couple weeks later. I don't want to be
selfish, but that's really [__]
awkward for all of us. You know what I
mean? We've already said congrats.
Um, and everybody knows, you know, you
are supposed to wait at least 3 months
before you announce the pregnancy
because that's how you know you're going
to carry your baby full term, right? U
me personally, I like to wait all the
way up until I'm throwing it in a
dumpster. Um, because I feel like before
then it's nobody's business.
It's called HIPPA. Look it up.
Sometimes that joke bums people out. So,
I want to like keep it super positive
right now and let you guys know that
she's pregnant again. And
yeah, she's pregnant again. And this
time we're at the five month mark. You
know what I mean? So, we know that she's
going to carry this baby full term. I've
been so excited. I've been marching
around work being like, "Guys, isn't
this so cool? Like, sometimes we're
going to have a little baby boy visiting
us at work." And she actually confronted
me and she was like, "Hey, I would
really appreciate it if you stopped
gendering my baby." And I was like, "I'm
sorry. I thought cuz you were naming it
Anthony that it was going to be a boy."
And she was like, "Well, the sex is
male, but we don't know about the gender
just yet." And I was like, "Okay." Um,
you know, that's it. You're trying to
get me in one of those 2025 traps. You
know what I mean? You're trying to get
me in that [__] [__] So, hey, look,
I want to be a good person. I've changed
what I'm saying completely. I've been
going around work being like, "Guys, did
you hear about Jen? She's having a
little baby rapist."
Cuz we all know what I'm saying, right?
It's going to have a penis.
I feel like you didn't laugh hard enough
for that joke. And
and it's a really good joke because it
pisses off people on both sides. You
know what I mean?
Because if you're super woke and you
hear me say gender, you're like, you
know. Um, but then also very gratifying
is telling it in front of straight white
frat bros cuz they'll all be like,
"We're not all rapists." You know, and
they'll say that to you when their dick
is halfway down your throat.
Oh my god, I got raped in that one. I
don't know. I'm so sorry. Um,
I'm so horny.
Are you guys uh are you guys on the
apps? Are we are we out there? Cuz I'm
out there and it's it's not good. It's
very bad. It's very bad. Um I went on a
date with a guy who told me that um he
was autistic. And guys, uh let's just be
real. I know we're in Brooklyn and
everyone is super like uh you know, but
isn't it crazy how thirsty everyone is
to be autistic nowadays?
It's insane. We never could have
predicted this when we were kids. You
know what I mean? We never could have
foreseen this coming that it would one
day be cool to be aut and and I think
it's just for attention. You know what I
mean? Because a couple years ago all the
girls were being like, "I'm bisexual."
And it's like, and then now they're
being like, "I'm autistic." And it's
like, "Hey, why don't you get up here
and show me how gay and [__] you
are?
[__] me.
[__] [__]
Yeah,
I'm sorry. I'm really I am so horny. Are
you guys um
are you [__] with the step porn?
Don't lie. Don't [__] get quiet when
I ask you that. There's a reason it's
number one on every [__] website out
there. And I didn't make a number one by
myself. I will tell you that. No, we all
did that. We all did that. It's gotten
so crazy. It's It's like to the point
where like families, I don't trust them.
Not at all. If I'm driving down the
street and I see a family enjoying each
other's company, I'm like, "Look at
these [__] perverts.
They're about to do it in that crosswalk
at 2:00 in the afternoon. That's sick."
I don't know. If you watch too much
porn, it starts making you dumb. You
know what I mean? Do you guys feel that?
All right, I guess I'm alone on that.
I'm taking in so much porn, it's
starting to alter the way that I
understand information all the way
around. You know what I mean? I was
reading the news the other day and I saw
this article and the headline said
94year-old woman passes oral exam for
United States citizenship.
And I was like, she shouldn't have to do
that.
94 years old. Let her in.
That's somebody's Abua.
I'm Ali May. Thank you so much.
>> How are we?
>> Yeah. I'm going to say this. Just get
this out of the way. This shirt's too
tight.
I didn't plan it. I didn't want that. I
wore it. I got in the car and I felt
everything and then I was like, "Oh my
god, I think the shirt's too tight." I
was like, "It's okay. You got a shirt in
the trunk." No shirt in the trunk. So,
for the taping, you get this.
There she is. There's the old girl.
There's the old girl. Yeah. Yeah, man.
This has been nuts. This has been um um
I don't know, man. I'll just tell you
what's going on. I just had two kids in
two years.
>> I had sex three times. I don't want to
talk about that.
It's upsetting. And I'm going to look at
you now. I see these young people here.
I'm going to tell you some [__] about
kids that is crazy. You love them so
much for no reason.
I love my kids more than anything. I
thought I love my wife. [__] that [__]
I love these kids.
But they don't deserve it. They're
ruining my life. They're ruining it. I'm
getting fatter. I'm not sleeping
anymore. I'm broke again. Look at me.
Look at me.
I'm 22 years old.
[Laughter]
They destroyed me. And they're in first
place. They don't deserve first. My wife
deserves first. My wife put the time in.
My wife had my back through all the
[__] She had my back when I started
in comedy. And when I started in comedy,
things were not going well.
All right. Things are still not going
that well. That's fine.
No, things were not going well. There
was a time in comedy I made $7,000
for the year.
For the year. Do you know who makes
$7,000 a year? People who die in
February.
That is who makes that kind of money. It
was me and a guy with a good month and a
drinking problem.
But you love him.
I don't even know why. what you do and
it's crazy. And my wife, we don't
communicate well. I I I don't know. She
texted me. I never know what she's
doing. She texted me [__] She texted me
the other day. She goes, "Hey, just so
you know, our son is an 8.5." And I was
like, "Well, first of all, our son is a
10." Okay. The hell are you talking
about? She's like, "He's not a 10. And
if you act like he's a 10, he's going to
[__] him up." And I was like, "No,
you're going to [__] him up by saying
he's not a 10. Let's boost his
confidence. I'm not a 10. I'm a six. But
I'm funny and I got you right. You're a
10." And she goes, "I'm not a 10. I'm an
eight." I said, "I hate this [__]
Bring yourself down. You're a 10. Say
it. I'm a 10." And she's like, "I'm not
a 10. I'm an eight." And you are an 11
and a half. And I went, "Wait, what the
[__] are you talking about?"
And she was like, "Our kids shoe size.
What were what were you talking about?"
And I was like, "How [__] our son
was."
I was kind of mad you didn't want to
[__] our son as much as I want to [__]
our son. That's a riff I'm never going
to do again. That just came out. Glad we
take that. Lag. Glad we take that. Don't
edit it. Put it out. All content is Let
that be. Maybe that's the kind of comic
I'll be known as.
Maybe that's the [__] image I've been
trying to go. That's the branding. That
guy wants to [__] his kid. I don't care.
We're I'm leading in this bit.
Did you see that Italian guy? The
Italian guy. Little mozzarella.
>> No. No. The one who wears tight shirts
and talks about [__] I got to get out
of this. I got to get out. I I don't I
don't even want to do this. And not as
any of you. You're laughing. All of you
are laughing, but you are going like
this. No. No. Please. No. Your eyes are
diverted at my shoes. That whole bit.
And for you, we'll move on.
This is fun. This is fun. I don't know
why this is fun. This is great. I'll
tell you what's crazy is that the bad
gigs are how I make money. I make all of
the money that I make is through doing
very bad gigs. So, I work a lot in like
casinos. And let me tell you, it's not
good for your life to do comedy in
casinos because here you guys are here
for comedy or at least you've heard of
comedy or like you you you kind of want
to laugh like you're here. You're a good
crowd. But no one in a casino sees
comedy because they like comedy. They go
because they're hemorrhaging so much
money they need to stop the bleeding for
one hour. And you try doing crowd work
with those people. You see how fun that
is? is like, "Where you from?" The guy's
like, "I don't know what I'm going to
tell my wife."
They're like, "You got kids?" And you're
like, "She's going to take the kids.
They're horrible, horrible gigs to do."
So, the only way to get through them is
I just get really high. I just get super
high because they're not going to laugh
anyway. So, I'll just have a good time.
I'm stoned for the full week I'm there.
What's crazy is that in New Jersey, they
have a smoking section. So, you could
smoke weed in the smoking section, which
is crazy that you're just walking around
getting high and it's not a problem, you
know? So, I was getting high and uh I
was I was I was sneak I was sneaking in
at first, you know. I was getting high
behind this little slot machine and uh I
I turn I turn around and there's a
72-year-old man in a Trump hat, Trump
shirt, Trump pants. Not going to be
honest. You vote for Trump, I don't give
a [__] But pants, that's too much.
That's too much.
If you like anything so much that you're
wearing the pants of that thing, you
like that thing too much. I love
Spider-Man. I show up on stage,
Spider-Man pants. You're like, "That's a
mentally handicapped person." He is.
He's funny. I support him. He drove
here. But that man is missing something.
So, I'm super high. He's yelling at me.
But you ever had that move where you're
so high you turn around and then you
just realize they've been talking to you
the whole time? Like I turned around,
the guy was like and I was like, "Hey."
And he was like, "I don't like weed."
And I was like, "Whoa, you How much did
you say? I was here."
And he's yelling at me and he's going,
"I don't want to smell that shit." But I
was so high. I went, "Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa."
I said, "You stop it right now." I even
put my finger on his lips. I did the
shut up and kiss me. I said, "Shut up
and kiss me." I put my finger on his
lips and I said, "We were sold a lie.
It's not the big deal they've told us it
was. It's actually kind of fun." And he
was like, "That's a gateway drug,
right?" And I said, "Stop it.
Who are you here with?" And he was like,
"My wife." And I was like, "Where is
she?" I'm like so intense, right? And he
was like, "She's in a bed sleeping." And
I said, "Okay, so you're by yourself,
right? She's sleeping. You got a room,
so you're safe. What if
you were to get a little high with me
right now. If you like it, you can keep
doing it. If you don't, at least you
know what you're fighting for.
Yeah. And this guy, he looks at me and
he just goes,
"Okay."
This is going to be unbelievable, right?
I gave him my vape pen. He took the
biggest hit I've ever seen in my life.
He was like, he just kept going. I'm
like, you're still pulling. He's like,
literally, he breathed out and his hat
spun off his head. It just spun around.
Just flew right off.
So, I'm like with this guy. I'm very I'm
very high. And uh and uh I got the light
for a second and I forgot where I was
going with this joke. So, we'll edit
this out. Uh we're not going to edit
this out. Nothing even matters in my
life. Uh, so
he's super high. I'm with him and I'm
like, "All right, I got to be a good
sherpa, right? I got to I can change
this guy's life. Marijuana could change
this guy's life." So I'm like, "All
right, man. Like, what kind of music do
you like?" Right? Cuz I'm going to give
him music. You know, you're first with
music. That's a big thing, right? So I
was like, "What kind of music you like?"
He goes, "Pink Floyd." I was like, "Wait
a minute. You like Pink Floyd? You've
never been high." I'm like, "Brother,
hang the [__] on." Right? I give him my
headphones and then he just goes, "I've
never heard Pink Floyd before." I'm
like, "I know. Marijuana is
unbelievable."
Then I'm like, "All right, I got to get
this guy food. I got to get this guy
food, right?" So I sneak him into the
employee cafeteria, right? And I gave
him ice cream. I got pizza. I give him
this ice cream. And he licks it and he
looks at me and he goes, "Is this what
it's like being a Democrat?"
And I was like, "Yeah, hell yeah,
brother. This is exactly what it's like.
We just get high and eat ice cream all
day. This is why we can't get [__] done.
All right, but this is this is what
we're doing.
We're high. I'm have a high combo with
this guy. Maybe I can get in there,
change his views. Let's see if I can
open up a little bit. Right. So, I'm
like, "Hey, man. Gay marriage. What do
you think? You in? You out? What are we
doing?" Right? And he goes, "I don't
know. You love who you love. You can
marry who you want. I don't really
care." And I was like, "Okay, all right.
Let's turn the heat up a little bit."
And I was like, "All right, trans. You
in? You out? How we doing? What What's
your thoughts? Trans. Let's go." I was
screaming at him.
And he was like, "Look, man. I don't
know, but I got to be honest. If if I
was hooking up with a chick and found
out she had a dick, I would freak out."
And I was like, "First of all, you're 72
years old. When is this happening? When
is this story taking place that you're
on the mix and you're meeting women and
some of them have penises and some
don't? This is a crazy situation that
you've made up in your head, right? And
then he goes, "What would you do? What
would you do?" And this [__] has
the wrong guy. All right?
Because I am the Christopher Columbus of
sexuality.
I don't believe in sexuality. I I'm not
gay or straight. I just haven't yet met
the man I want to [__] All right?
That's where I'm at. a man hasn't
stepped up to the challenge. That's
where I'm at. Right? So, he's like,
"What would you do?" Right? And I was
like, "Well, let's talk about it for a
second." Right? Okay. So, you're telling
me in your scenario, you met a woman who
you thought was beautiful enough from
head to toe that you would sleep with
her, cool enough that you would hang out
with her and then also sleep with her.
But there was one piece, one piece you
didn't like. There was one piece. And he
was like, "Yeah, it's a big piece." And
I was like, "All right, but look, look
at this piece of pizza, right? I love
pizza.
I hate mushrooms. So you do what I do if
I was eating pizza and I found this
mushroom.
Eat around it.
And I swear to God, this guy just goes
and you [__] nailed it, baby.
All right, I got to do I got to do one
more because I did too much riffing up
front and I wanted to get the I got to
tell the story because I I don't know.
I'm very excited about it. So, I'm doing
this club uh with this old school
comedian, right? This guy's been doing
comedy since the 80s. This guy's been
doing cocaine for 40 years straight. Has
not stopped. He's the most [__] up
human I've ever met. And he's like 70
years old. And I'm like, this [__]
guy is wild, right? So, show's over and
he looks at me, he goes, "Hey, you want
to go get pizza and do magic?"
And I was like, "Look, man. I don't got
money for pizza, but I definitely want
to see some [__] magic." And he goes,
"Oh, hang on. and I got this. Walks over
to a slot machine, puts money in, pulls
it, wins $37.50,
and just goes, "Let's go." He
He didn't even react. I was like, "Is
that the magic?" Because that was
unbelievable.
We walked to this pizza place in the
casino, right? And for 40 minutes, it
takes 40 minutes for them to make this
pizza. For 40 minutes, he is doing up
close magic to me.
not getting a single trick right. Every
single trick. Every single trick. He was
like, "And that's why the king loves his
queen." And I was like, "That's a three.
That's a two, man. What are we doing,
brother?" He was like, "Oh, but the
queen always loves her diamonds." And
I'm like, "That's an empty. You just
show me your fat belly, brother."
Okay.
So then he just passes out. We eat the
pizza. He's passed out at the table. I'm
by myself. I'm like, "This is crazy."
Right? Waiter comes with the check, puts
the check down. I open the check. The
check is for $37.50.
The exact amount of money he won on that
magic slot machine. And he out of a coma
just goes,
"Tada."
I was like, that is the most
unbelievable thing I've ever seen in my
life. Was the whole thing a trick? Am I
a trick? I'm Greg Stone. You guys were
so much fun. Thank you.
>> I'm like rediscovering myself. You know
what kind of person am I now that I live
alone and it turns out uh I'm the kind
of person that yells, "Let's go at
everything."
You know what I mean?
Am I heating up egg rolls? Let's go.
You know, just Law and Order original
recipe. Let's [__] go. I'm so into
it. Everything's a sporting event. Just
let's go. While I'm wearing like one
piece of clothing, you know? It's like a
a tank top or a or a sock
or actually it's a compression. I'm like
62% compression sleeves right now. You
know, when you're young, it's about
letting it all hang out, but when you
get older, it's about gathering it all
back up,
putting it where it used to go.
I uh I I had a roommate. I had a
roommate and um he moved. He fell in
love with a woman who owns her property.
So
all right dreams. So uh so he left he
left he left a lot of stuff behind
almost all of his furniture you know he
left his television behind. He left
behind his towels.
Yeah. And when I said to him, "Hey bro,
um aren't you going to take your
towels?" He said to me, "Well, I mean
she's got towels.
I was like, "Oh, I didn't realize I've
been raising you this whole time.
I thought we were two people trying to
make it in the big city." But turns out
I was trying to keep you alive in front
of a PS5, I guess.
He did take the PS5, so important
things. So, he's gone. And uh this means
I'm uh I'm ready for love.
I am. I'm ready for love because I've uh
I've got the room, you know.
I've got my room with my bed that I
sleep on. And then I guess I got his old
room with his old bed for threesomes.
It's a queen-sized bed. What am I
supposed to do with all that space? It's
so much. I guess I can be part of a
thrpple if we all curl up in the fetal
position. You know that's my favorite
sexual position.
The fetal position with a donkey kick
chaser.
Get off me.
I'm very confusing. Uh
oh my gosh. Yeah, I am. I'm I'm ready
for for love, I think. Like I'm not
looking for it.
Um, I just thought maybe I could
manifest a little something something. I
don't know. Write it on a post-it note.
I'm not sure. I didn't really do the
research, but like I'm not looking for
love on my phone. Well, that's where I
read my fanfiction.
Can't get those confused, you know?
But I really think I'm like the best
version of me right now. And I'm quite a
catch. Like it's not going to get better
than this, you know? Like both of my
parents are dead, so no baggage. Come
on. Come on.
I'm plum out of eggs, so no whoopsies.
You know,
sounding better and better. I'm sounding
better and better.
[Music]
I live alone. Come on, let's do it. Oh,
why not? You know, I just I didn't think
at this particular age I would be alone,
you know. Not that I had a vision that I
would be like married. I just figured
I'd trick some some schlub into, you
know what I mean? Breadcrumbs, you know?
I thought I'd get somebody.
I don't know, man. I I mean, I knew I
wouldn't have any kids because um when I
was 12, I thought to myself,
you know what? I shouldn't have any kids
because I'll probably be a single mom.
I thought that at 12.
My parents
never divorced.
I'm not from a broken home. Home still
together, you know. I just I just knew
that I was a bit of a pill.
So,
so ridiculous, you know, but I am I
figured why not? Why not? Let's look for
a little something. I want to be very
particular about what I'm looking for
though in a mate, you know, like I want
to have inside jokes with a person. Do
you know what I mean? Like, I want us to
speak the same language. I want us to be
like completely insufferable. That's
what I want. I don't know if you've ever
said anything to a couple and uh and
they look at each other and they go,
"That's
that's what I want." Oh, I want to be a
pain in your ass. I I once was hanging
out with my parents, right? Uh I'm at
their house. We're watching some music
show and then uh you guys remember Neo?
Remember R&B's Neo?
>> Yes. Okay. So he came out and he started
singing a song and my mom turned to my
dad and she went, "There he goes with
that hat
and then they laughed for like 30
minutes."
I was like, "Should I even be here?" Oh
god. So that's what I want. I want the
kind of inside jokes that make my grown
daughter uncomfortable. That's what I
want. You know, I've been doing uh I've
been doing some research on the love
languages, you know, how you tend to
display your love. And uh I think I'm a
physical touch person. Like yeah, I
think I just
that's what I want, you know? I just
like I wear extremely high-waisted
pants, so it feels like there's a hand
in the small of my back
just leading me around Whole Foods, you
know,
helping me pick out olives
cuz olives is a couple's food. I think
we can agree, right, that olives is a c
any food that you like toss in your
mouth and you also throw your foot up.
That's a move that you only do with the
confidence of somebody else who can call
the right people.
You don't do that when you live alone.
You do not do that when you live alone.
Unless, of course, you have the chair.
And by the chair, I mean when you live
alone, you have the chair that you throw
yourself on.
So that when you start choking, you
can't give yourself the himlet. So you
got to throw yourself on the chair. So,
if you don't live alone,
that's a tip from me to you.
Get yourself a chair. You know, you know
what? I'll throw in another tip. Uh, if
you live alone, you should probably
lounge around in your house in the kind
of outfit you want to be discovered in.
Do you know what I mean? When they kick
the door open, what's the tale you're
going to tell?
That's what that is. So that's what I
want. I want inside jokes. I want loving
touches. I want olives. I want to
reluctantly go down on a dude because
it's Thursday and we agreed that was our
date night even though that doesn't
really work for my schedule because I
work from home on Wednesday. So I'm
thinking we could do it in the daytime.
I'm not going to wash it all off. But
then why are you available to have sex
in the middle of the day? Where's your
job, sir?
It's too late. I like them. So, here I
am, you know, kind of tired on a
Thursday just gawking on this guy.
[Applause]
Real romance. That's all I'm asking for.
Real romance. That's all I want, you
know? And I mean, I'll wait, but I can't
wait too long because uh time is kind of
the essence. like I am currently making
the transition from a pink vibrator
to a black vibrator.
And that feels ominous, doesn't that?
It feels a little weird. I mean, it's a
literal vibe shift. I don't know.
It just it just feels like uh when I was
a child I played with childish things.
You know what I mean? That's what it
feels like.
[Music]
I'm also uh I'm not trying to get with
anyone my age.
Not doing it. I already know what Lipur
does. I'm not talking to any dude who
takes it. You know what I mean? I mean,
I want to talk to someone younger. You
know what? What are your new pills? What
are y'all taking? Don't you want to see
how it interacts with hypertension?
Let me be here for you. You know, the
last time I did anything with a dude my
age, gh it was a longdistance sexing
situationship.
I think I think those are the correct
terms. And I put them in the right
order. You're nodding. I think I think I
did. Yeah. I mean, all that is is just
two Gen X people sending each other
dirty messages on Facebook. That's all
that is. Just ah, you know what I'mma do
to you? You know, I better stretch.
That's all. That's all that is. Just
dirty, dirty, filthy, dirty, filthy. And
then he died.
Yeah. Sudden heart attack. Do you
understand what I'm up against? I don't
have that kind of time. Like the only
thing hardening were his arteries. I'm
up against steak. I can't You'll never
win against steak, you know. So, he's
gone.
But he did.
But he did change my views on ghosting.
That's enough out of me. I'm Chalet was
sharp. Thank you very much. Very
quickly, um, I'm real into fashion.
That's why I'm dressed like a white guy,
dressed like a Japanese guy, dressed
like a white guy.
I know I dress like uh someone who hunts
men for sport, you know, like
you'll do, you know, like
No, I'm very lucky. I uh I'm I'm
blessed. Okay. I got two kids at home. I
got two kids. So, I'm rich in love. I'm
rich in love. Yeah. I'm poor by every
other metric. I'm poor. Money, property,
hemoglobin. Don't got any hemoglobin? No
blood. It's crazy. It's tough having
kids, man. You know how I know it's
tough having kids? Uh at the airport,
the only two groups of people they let
on an airplane early are uh young
parents and uh active military. Okay. Do
you know how many times I've been on a
jet bridge? It's me, my two kids, my
wife, and then a guy who lost his leg in
Fallujah.
And we're both looking at each other
like, "At least I'm not you." You know
what I'm saying? Like,
that's a fun one.
When my my son was born, I was going
around. I was telling everybody, "Oh, we
had a baby. We had a baby." But really,
my wife had a baby, you know, cuz women
are amazing. What? My wife, she birthed
this life, right? She created this life.
She fed this life with her own body and
I called the Uber to the hospital, you
know. I mean on her account, but I
called it. I mean, I was like, "How far
was uh part of those contractions?"
Because uh storage pricing is crazy
right now.
90 seconds. We're good.
Little contraction joke for you guys. Um
the [__] up thing is that my uh son
has my last name. That's [__] up.
That's right. Having a kid with me must
feel like the ultimate school group
project. You guys know what I'm talking
about? You know the those projects where
somebody else does all the work in the
very last second? I'm like,
before you turn that in and put my name
on that,
I went to one meeting at the very
beginning. I worked hard for two
minutes. I deserve credits.
My wife is Korean. I'm Vietnamese. Uh,
real quick, where my Koreans at? Where
my Koreans at?
No, no, that's perfect. I don't trust
Korean people. That's why I want to know
where they at. Okay.
Okay. We're going to have to bleep this
part of the video out. But it's going to
be real in a second. No, I uh I'm
Vietnamese and my wife is Korean, so we
were very worried about how our son was
going to look. We had never seen that
combo before. And you all have never
seen that combo before. I've never seen
I've seen every combo. Okay. I've seen a
white guy with a Japanese woman. I've
seen uh a Malaysian woman with a white
guy. I've seen
every combo, but I've never seen
Korean Vietnamese before. Right. And I
didn't know this, but apparently if you
mix one kind of Asian with another kind
of Asian, the baby comes out extremely
Asian.
All right. A Vietnamese and a Korean
makes a Mongolian. I didn't know that
he came out of my wife on a horse. I was
like, "Oh shit."
His best friend's a hawk. I was like,
"Holy [__] he's sick."
My son is cool, man. My son is uh when
he was little, he was he was fat and he
had little eyes. He had big old ears,
big old belly. You know what he looked
like? He looked like one of those fat
Buddhist statues that white women keep
in their bathrooms,
you know, to balance the fune. Is he He
really did look like that. That's why I
was afraid of taking him places like
Pier One Imports, you know.
I was I was afraid someone was going to
be like, "Sir, you going to pay for that
fat booty statue?"
And I was like, "Uh, this is my son.
Let's get out of here."
Okay,
a hawk comedy here. This murder is in
Mongolia. Um,
we had our we had our children I had my
son through IVF, which uh I think is
pretty kinky. I think that's pretty
high. You know, we're in Brooklyn. A lot
of Brooklyn people, they want to spice
up their relationship. They invite a
third in. My wife and I, we're like,
"Let's invite the whole health care
system in."
Yeah. You guys ever been cucked by Mount
Si? You guys ever
You guys ever pay someone $15,000 to get
your wife pregnant? That's
Yeah,
that's my kink co-ay. Yeah, that's
that's some hot [__] This is a smart
crowd. Okay. um
took us a long time to have our child or
to have our son and uh took us years and
years, many many cycles, many many
retrieval cycles, many many attempts and
uh we were down to just one embryo,
right? And so the doctor calls us in and
he says, "We only got one embryo left.
You got one more shot at this." But then
he says something I'll never forget. He
looks me right in the eye and he goes,
"But this embryo is really high
quality."
And I was like, "When did we start
talking about embryos?" Like I talk
about my weed, you know? Like he's like,
he's like, "No, dude. Check out Dude,
check out this embryo, dude. Smell the
crystals on this embryo, dude. So,
you're going to get so pregnant, dude.
I love it."
Yeah. My son, uh, we we had a son and we
thought we only had one shot. We were
grateful to just have one. They were
doing going through the records and uh
we realized that actually at the very
beginning of this years and years ago.
We actually had had another embryo that
we froze and we kept that frozen for
five years and then we decided to
unfreeze it and then in August of last
year we had a daughter. Yeah, that's
cool, right? I know. I [__] I love
that story because it's it's my about my
daughter. But I really like it because
that is the most Asian way to do IVF I
have ever heard. Okay, leave it to an
Asian couple to be like, "Oh, you
thought we were out of embryos? Check
the other fridge.
Go down to the basement. Open the
fridge. Move the kimchi over. There's an
embryo.
While you're at it, go ahead and bring
the kimchi up, too."
My son is uh is uh three now. He's a
toddler. Um he's three and uh I live in
Brooklyn and I can't take my son
anywhere because I didn't know this, but
toddlers are not woke.
You guys know this. Toddlers are not
woke at all. My son's favorite thing,
this is true, my son's favorite thing is
the NYPD.
He loves the police.
Every time a cop car goes by, he's like,
"Bluey, lives matter." I was like, "I
don't know who taught him that [__]
Rogan's getting mixed up into the
YouTube list." You know,
it's true. It's true. My son uh loves
the NYPD, the FDNY, and the Department
of Sanitation. My son loves municipal
services. Okay. He may live in Brooklyn,
but his heart is in Staten Island. All
right. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I don't know why you guys
are clapping. None of you guys are from
Stan Island.
>> It's cool, man. I do. I love it. I um
I'm not a very uh good Asian person. Um
my mom is here. I guess that's
not a very good Asian person. I'm not a
very good Asian person because I don't
speak the language. Uh I don't speak uh
Vietnamese. And it's a bummer because um
we're not supposed to tell you this, but
when we don't want to talk to white
people, uh we just pretend to speak the
other language. Asian people do that.
All right. And I can't do that. Right.
So I do the next best thing. I speak the
language I can kind of speak, which is
um the language the Jaba the Hut speaks
in Star Wars.
Yeah. If somebody starts messing with me
on the subway, I'm just like Njaba
Noada.
Uh, Kachon Kawuki.
A lot of beautiful people here. I'm
happy to be here. A lot of beautiful
people here.
Makes me nervous though. I was talking
to um uh this is a while ago. I was
talking to um after a show. I was
talking to this beautiful woman at uh
after the show and I was talking to her
for a while and I realized while I was
talking to her that uh she was a preop
transgender woman, a pre-operative
transgender woman. She was gorgeous. And
I told my friends all about her. I was
like, "She was so pretty." And they were
like, "Preop? Doesn't that mean you're a
little bit gay, man?"
And uh I don't think so at all. I think
it means the opposite. Okay? It means I
love women. Okay? I love women so much.
I even love women who are just beginners
at being women. Okay?
Right? I got so much love for the game.
I don't just watch professionals. Okay?
I keep an eye on those upand cominging
prospects.
Let me tell you something. I love women
so much. If a woman is hot enough, I'll
suck her dick. Okay,
[Music]
that is a straight as hell thing to say.
All right,
real quick. Uh, I am Vietnamese. I I
like to tell people I'm Vietnamese
upfront because Asian people, we don't
like it when uh you guys guess what kind
of Asian we are. We don't like that
because a lot of times you guys get it
wrong. Um, but we also don't like it
because sometimes you guys get it right.
Uh, that sucks. Okay. Like one day, uh,
I was at, uh, out somewhere. I was at a
bar and this bartender saw me, clocked
me right away. He's like, Vietnamese.
And I was like, "Fuck,
well, you know the rules. I owe you a
wish." Um,
Honda Civic. All right. My name is Mike
Dway. You guys have been great. Thank
you so much.
>> My name is Nory. Um, I'll just get into
it. I'm a trans American.
>> Yes.
Uh, it's it's illegal now.
Oh, it's okay.
It's okay. It's fine. I I recently
started um a really good uh
anti-depressant
uh called Symbalta.
Anyone else?
>> Not that a different one.
It's really I highly recommend.
It's so good. Earlier this year, there
were a lot of like attacks on the trans
community. Are you guys aware of that?
And uh while that was happening, I just
started the Symbalta.
So, I was watching the news and I was
like,
that is so bad
for them.
[Laughter]
If that if that happened to me, I I'd
kill myself.
It's okay.
It's okay. I started transitioning uh
when Obama was president.
So, I feel bamboozled.
Uh,
didn't read the contract.
[Laughter]
Your rights can go away
in like not a lot of time. Actually,
the Obama period was different for trans
people. Like, do you guys remember the
Virgin Atlantic commercials?
Oh, I miss those.
You know the ones where like
like the camera goes to the cockpit and
and the pilot's a a trans woman and
she's just like
[Laughter]
and you're like, is she even a pilot?
But I'm scared. I'm scared. Oh,
you can laugh.
You can laugh. Give permission. Um,
No, it's okay. It's fine. If they do
start putting us into camps, um, I hope
it's outside.
I want to be outside.
Actually,
I think actually I know what they're
going to do. I know. I think they're
going to
uh put us on an island. That's like a
big
Do you work here?
The transphobia is crazy in America.
They don't even want me to say what I
have to say.
>> What I was going to say is I think
they're going to put trans people on
like a big island that's like a big
Sephora.
[Laughter]
And I think um we're going to have to
color match
uh foundation for sis women.
>> And if we if we get it wrong, they're
going to kill us.
It's okay.
No, a lot a lot of bad stuff happened
this year to trans people. But I'm very
lucky cuz I have a lot of people in my
life that are really good allies.
Like I had a lot of people that were
like, "Whatever happens, like I got your
back." Um,
but these people also smoke a lot of
weed.
Like the person that was like, "I got
your back." I'm like, "You're literally
never sober."
Like like if the police came for me and
they opened the door, they'd be like,
"Oh, yeah, she's right here."
I was pretty freaked out earlier this
year. I I got a I got a safe.
Anyone ever buy a safe before?
[Laughter]
You know what I'm talking about.
the LGBTs who are like, I know what
you're talking about.
Uh, I bought a safe on on Amazon. Sorry.
Sorry.
I didn't I didn't know where else to go.
Um,
I bought a safe on Amazon. And what's so
funny about buying a safe is this is
what I realized. The safe was too big to
like hide.
like I couldn't hide it anywhere,
but it was light enough to carry.
So, so essentially I'm I'm like making
like like a to-go bag.
So, I just got a gun.
Um,
yeah. I think technology is changing my
brain. Anyone else?
>> The other day I was out to dinner with
my friend and like they're not a
comedian so they don't know how to tell
stories.
They're like you guys.
[Music]
Yeah. So,
my friend was telling me like a really
uh boring story about their grandma or
something and without even thinking I
swiped up.
Isn't that crazy?
Like it like I was literally listening.
I was just like
[Music]
I have a gun. Um
I uh I'm on a wellness journey.
You guys are like, "Prove it."
And by that I mean I started uh doing
ketamine.
Anyone else?
A very quiet. Yeah.
Who?
Be proud.
It's amazing. And I listen, I do it
legit. Like, I do it the right way. I
get mine through a company
um called Choose Ketamine.
It's uh it's based out of Texas
>> and you zoom with a doctor
and he asks really um important medical
questions like um
do you want ketamine?
And like followup questions like uh
How much?
And then they send it to you to do it at
home
by yourself.
>> And the last time I did uh ketamine, it
was amazing. It's like out of body, like
you're like part of the universe. It's
so cool. And I was having a great time.
But then out of nowhere,
I was confronted with the fact that
sometimes I deal with being passively
suicidal.
But then I heard a voice and the voice
said, "But if you kill yourself,
you can't do any more ketamine.
[Music]
It works.
I'll leave you with this.
Okay. Um
I uh Sorry, I'm on ketamine.
Sorry.
I'll end with this and get out of here.
Um,
I'm working on impressions.
Thank you. Thank you.
Um, this is a minion.
Uh, coming out as bisexual.
Oh,
and sexual.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
>> I moved to Denver last year. I moved
from here to Denver. Thanks. It is uh
it's so dry there. It [__] sucks.
It's the driest place. Have you heard
about Denver? It's [__] so dry. If
you haven't heard, it's cuz you haven't
met someone from Denver, cuz it's all
they talk about, dude. They [__] love
the dry out there. They're like, "Oh,
isn't it great? Don't you love how dry
it is? Isn't it the dryest? I couldn't
live anywhere that's not this dry. Oh,
don't you just love?" No, I don't. I
have eczema. All right. I'm about to
turn to ash.
It sucks. I had to use lotion for the
first time on my body.
I've used lotion before, but not on my
arms. I didn't even know you could do
that. What a world.
Lotion budget through the roof right
now. I'm drowning in lotion debt.
I'm happy to be back in New York. I miss
New York. I miss bodegas. We don't have
bodegas in Denver. I try to explain it
to my friends in Denver. I'm like, "It's
like a 7-Eleven, but the guy at the
counter is playing the Price is Right."
You know, you like put everything up
there and he's like
11.
Is that dollars or He's like, "Shut up.
I'm on the phone.
Don't let the cat out.
>> Happy to be back, though. Uh, I'm a I
sleep on my stomach. Any other freaks
out there?
Oh, all right. We got some belly
sleepers. Yeah, some loud and proud
belly sleepers in the back. The rest of
you normal.
We're wrong. It turns out if you sleep
on your belly, that's not how humans
were made. It turns out I think you're
weird if you can sleep on your back. You
just like lay down in your eyes closed
like a doll. That's creepy.
You sleep on your back. How do you fall
asleep looking at your phone? It's going
to break your nose.
I sleep on my I was trying to find a new
mattress. I asked them what kind of
mattress I should get if I sleep on my
stomach. They're like, "Don't do that.
What do you What's wrong with you?
That's not how Yeah. I sleep I sleep on
my stomach. I sleep face [__] down,
dude. I don't even I I tuck my arms
under me and sleep like a missile.
I sleep like I'm trying to touch the
deep end. You know what I mean? I'm
trying to get as deep. This is the only
way I could put my phone down is to lock
myself up. I don't even look to the
side. I look down. I look into If I fall
asleep looking to the right, I can't
look to the left for seven days. I
can't. Honestly, my dream bed, one of
those massage tables with the hole for
your face. That would be Give me a
massage chair and a straight jacket. It
would be the best night of sleep I've
ever had
in my life. I sleep on my stomach, so
the devil has a way to get in. That's
right.
I think I I think it's why I'm single is
because I'm a stomach sleeper. Cuz you
can't share a bed with someone you love
and sleep on your stomach. It doesn't
work. Because you want to go to sleep,
but you got to show affection. Sometimes
you're like, "All right, here comes the
cuddle. Here we are."
Now, trust me, I like this, too. I'm
about to fall asleep any second.
But you can't date someone who also
sleeps on their stomach, cuz then you're
just two strangers
sharing a bed. There's no love. It's
perfect.
Yeah. Yeah, I don't have one of those
massage, but I do sleep face down. So, I
just take two pillows. I make a little
nook for my head. I make a little bed
[__] I put my face put my face right
in the bedussy. And I sleep like a baby,
dude. It's
You got to take care of yourself. You
sleep face down. I bought myself linen
sheets. Everyone like, "These are the
softest sheets money can buy." I put
them on. Little scratchy. I'm not going
to lie. I thought it'd be like
immaculate. Someone told me you got to
wash linen sheets a few times. After you
wash them four to five times, you're
sleeping on clouds. And it's like, I got
to wait four years to sleep on clouds.
I'm [__]
I wish you told me that or we're stuck
with the bamboo.
Yeah, I sleep face down, so my back
hurts all the [__] time. It hurts.
Uh, have you ever had your back hurt so
much that you thought if you hung
yourself that just for a second
that that would feel so good, dude? That
would be there would just be a flash of
everything being aligned as it could
never be again.
Your last thoughts would be there it is.
And then
sweet release.
Yeah, I got a problem with my phone. I
can't stop looking. I'm trying to cut
down on my phone screen time. I'm trying
to get it down under eight hours a day.
I think that that would be healthier.
You get those notifications on Sunday.
They're like, check out your phone
screen time. And you open it, they're
like, 8 and 1/2 hours.
I haven't slept for 8 and 1/2 hours in
my whole life.
What am I doing? I'm working Instagram
like a full-time job. It is. I'm worried
that when millennials when we're in
nursing homes, that's what they're going
to give us. Like we're not going to get
the cool psycho drugs, they're just
going to give us Facebook.
That's going to be our like winding down
years. They'll come in like Mr. Comtock.
I see you've only scrolled for 4 hours
today. I'm like, I wanted to look out
the window. They're like, it's not your
world anymore, Mr. Contock.
Strap them down, boys. I'm like,
how did I get on Christian Tik Tok
again?
So,
that's about how I start every day right
now. It's kind of sucks.
I uh All right, cool.
Trying to check my time there. My heart
rate is accelerated. It turns out
you had your watch tell you you're
dying. I don't like this.
Any millennials in the crowd?
>> That was pretty lively. Usually it's
more of like a
We're beaten down, dude. We're the worst
generation. And that's probably true,
but it's not our fault. I don't blame
millennials. It's not totally our fault.
We got the internet at the wrong time.
All right. We got the internet when we
were like young teens. is like that's
not when you're sp like we're the only
generation that got [__] up by the
internet. You know that like boomers did
not get [__] up by the internet. They
still don't understand
how horrible of a place the internet is.
Like my mom still thinks Facebook is the
news. You know, she's like, "Oh, I was
reading an article." I'm like, "It's not
an article, Mom. That's a meme. It's
called
a meme. It's a AI cat with words on it.
It's not real.
My dad thinks spreading cheeks is
smiling. So it's They have no idea.
Millennials, we got [__] dude. I
watched Two Girls One Cup when I was 12
years old.
What hope did I have? I didn't even I
didn't even know there was like
[__] porn in the world. Like I didn't I
didn't even know what masturbating was.
I thought this was like girls version of
jackass or something. I was like, damn,
these chicks are crazy.
My parents, it's funny cuz now my
parents are Republicans and they're all
like worried about internet security all
of a sudden. They're like, "You got to
delete the cookies off the computer."
They're using Duck Duck. You got to get
rid of the cookies. I'm like, damn. I'm
glad you didn't know about cookies when
I was 13. Dude, that was I've been
deleting cookies off the computer since
you could use the internet, mom. All
right. I was there when it was written.
Millennials, that was our We got the
family computer. Kids, now they got an
iPad. It's nice. We got a family
computer. Everyone had to share. It was
10 ft from your mom's room.
I'll tell you one thing. No one can
check off like a millennial. We are pros
at checking out. I could jack off
without moving a muscle in my body. One
finger. A T-Rex wouldn't see me finish.
It would be amazing.
>> You guys are a lot of fun. My name is
Jack. Bye.
>> Just so you know where I'm at. I'm
feeling very insecure about my body
right now. I think I look pretty good
for somebody who had a kid 6 months ago.
But no, no, no. Sorry. Sorry. That
somebody is not me.
[Laughter]
It's just the scale I want to be graded
on. That's all.
No, I don't have kids, but I do have to
decide soon if I'm going to have a kid.
I keep getting asked if I'm going to
freeze my eggs, and then I have to
explain to those people that I can
barely afford eggs.
I'm at the age where when I'm with my
parents, I will very intentionally drink
alcohol in front of them so they don't
think I'm pregnant.
We went to my cousin's wedding a month
ago and I just didn't feel like
drinking. And my mom clocked it
immediately.
They came around and they were like,
"Champ?" And I was like, "No thanks. I'm
good." And my mom goes, "So,
is there something you want to tell me?"
And I was like, "Oh, she knows I'm on
mushrooms.
How does she always know?"
No, I don't know. I don't have a kid. I
can't take care of a kid. I can't take
care of another human being, right? I
can barely take care of myself. I just
learned my whole life I've been doing
oral hygiene.
Wrong. Cuz what you're supposed to do,
did you guys know this? What you're
supposed to do is you're supposed to
floss first, then mouthwash, then brush
the end. Did you guys all know that?
Okay, go. Thank you. I'm Some of you
did, but I feel very validated by those
of you who didn't, cuz I've probably
been doing what you've been doing. I
brush first, then I mouthwash, and then
I floss two days before my dentist
appointment
and act shocked that I'm bleeding.
I'm like, that's crazy. That's never
happened for me before. You did that.
That's wild.
>> No, I don't know. I live in New York.
Like, my apartment is not set up for
kids, right? I mean, honestly, it's not
set up for people.
>> The mice are doing well.
Has anybody here ever dealt with mice?
Has anybody here had a mouse problem?
Does anybody have any advice for me?
>> Get a cat.
>> Get a cat. Okay. Do you have a cat?
>> You're the most confident person in this
room. I just want you to know. A woman
with a cat. People love to make fun of a
woman with a cat. A woman with a cat is
the most confident person you will ever
meet because that is a person who can
handle rejection.
I mean it. Cats treat you like it is
last call at the bar.
They're the hottest girl and you are all
that's left.
They'll like walk by you, ignore you the
whole time, and then maybe if you're
lucky, they'll double back and be like,
"Okay, you can touch me, but not on the
stomach.
[Laughter]
It's a hot girl. I saw a poster for a
lost cat once and I was like, I think
that's just a cat that's moved on.
I was in Louisiana last week and
somebody told me to get a snake.
I can't have a snake. I don't have a
nipple piercing and 17 tattoos. So,
that's that's an issue. Now, I've been
trying to put like stuff in the traps
for these mice. Like, I put peanut
butter in the traps. Somebody told me I
should put peanut butter, but I had to
stop cuz I was like, "What if they have
an allergy?" And then
And then I was putting good cheese in
there. Like good. Like like Murray's
cheese. Like good [__] Like good. Cuz
that's how I want to go. If you gave me
a full wheel of Brie tonight, you can
snap my neck tomorrow.
I'll leave a note saying don't press
charges.
But it's New York. You know, that's the
price we pay. I've lived in New York now
for 10 years. And I'm not going to call
myself a New Yorker cuz people in New
York who were born here get very upset
if you call yourself a New Yorker and
you weren't born here. I think it's cuz
you still have a little bit of happiness
and they don't like that. There's always
some guy who's like, "I'm a New Yorker,
born and raised, always miserable."
Like, it's always that guy. So, I'm not
going to do that. But I will say the
first time I ever felt like a New
Yorker, I remember I was sitting on the
subway falling asleep and when I woke
up, there was a man standing in front of
me with his dick out. But I was so tired
that the only reaction I could muster up
was,
"Come on, man.
And then he went, "All right."
And put it away. And I was like, "No,
I did it. I made it. I'm a New Yorker.
I'm too exhausted to be sexually
harassed."
Also hilarious that he asked for
consent. I can't stop thinking about
like honestly that's one of the better
men in New York, you know.
No, I love I love living in New York
now. It took me a while, but I I I think
I I loved it the first time I
experienced Halloween here. Halloween in
New York is so fun cuz you get to try to
figure out like who's in costume and who
just looks like that, right? It's really
fun. Last year on Halloween, I saw a guy
dressed as Super Mario running to catch
the train
and he did not make it. the train closes
in his face and then somebody from
across the platform who saw the whole
thing yelled out, "Should have held down
B."
And that was mean of me, but I was just
like in a mood. I don't know. I grew up
in Kentucky and there's not a lot to do
in Kentucky, but we do have one cool
thing. We have Abraham Lincoln's
birthplace is in Kentucky and they
turned it into a museum. It's a cool
place you can go. I remember going
fairly often as a kid and then I went
back recently. I drove by it and they
have a new billboard up outside of
Abraham Lincoln's birthplace and it says
Abraham Lincoln never had the
opportunity to get vaccinated but you
do.
I was like sorry what?
Cuz don't get me wrong, I think that's
like a good message to have. I just
think Abraham Lincoln is the wrong
messenger,
right? That's like the one guy who
famously died of a shot.
>> No, I'm pro vaccine. I love a vaccine. I
want every vaccine. Give me vaccines.
People think vaccines cause autism.
That's why autism is on the rise. Autism
is not on the rise. We just have better
testing for it, right? That's that's all
it is. Autism is not on the rise because
we've been reading Amelia Bedilia since
the 60s.
Amelia Bedilia is a series about an
autistic woman trying to make it in a
neurotypical world and failing. But
that's just how far along we've come
with autism testing cuz now they have
like real tests. In the '9s they just
read the class Amelia Bedilia and then
they were like, "Who doesn't get why
this is funny?"
[Music]
And then you didn't see that kid again
until high school.
No, I love vaccines. I'm Jewish. Give me
Give me whatever you got. I My immune
system can't do anything on its own.
>> I love it. Have you guys heard this
phrase, we listen and we don't judge?
>> Okay. As a Jewish woman, I have never
related to a phrase less in my life
than we listen and we don't judge. Not
only am I judging, I'm not really
listening.
I love being Jewish. I really do. I love
being Jewish so much. And I would give
it all up in a heartbeat if I got to
genuinely celebrate Christmas. God,
Christmas is incredible. I Man,
Christmas. It's like um It's like It's
like Christmas. Like, it's so good.
There's not There's no Jewish holiday as
fun as Christmas. Most Christmas songs
were written by Jews
because Jews couldn't find a Jewish
holiday happy enough to write that
stuff. There's no cozy chestnuts
roasting on an open fire for Jews. It's
all just like Drreid. Like that's that's
just a song about a guy going up to a
child saying, "You want to learn how to
gamble?" Like it's not it's not cozy.
It's a song about rules.
There's no like equivalent of Jewish
Santa. Somebody once told me it's
Elijah. That's our Santa. But Elijah is
a ghost who shows up halfway through
dinner, drinks your alcohol, and leaves.
And that's not that's not Santa. That's
like the child of your most troubled
friend from seventh grade who like
you're still worried about. There's no
there's no Jewish Santa. So there Jewish
Santa would be such a bummer, right?
He's not going to come down the chimney.
He's just going to come through the
front door and be like, "I know your
mother."
Yeah. So, I'm I I grew up in Kentucky,
but I moved here from New Orleans.
That's where I that's where I used to
live. Um I loved living in New Orleans,
too, very much. Jazzfest is like this
really cool outdoor festival that I
would go to every year. And I remember
one year at Jazzfest. This is like why
you should go to live music, cuz cool
stuff will just happen. I went to
Jazzfest and I saw Stevie Wonder
perform. And while he was performing, it
was pouring down rain, but the show must
go on. And he started playing Ribbon in
the Sky, which is a song about a
rainbow. And halfway through the song,
the rain stopped and a rainbow came out.
And we went nuts. We got so loud. We
were cheer. We were like, "Oh my god,
it's a song about a rainbow." And a
rainbow came out. We could not believe
our We were like, "This is incredible.
This is life." But I also remember
thinking like, what does Stevie Wonder
think is happening right now?
He was just like, "Yeah, I really killed
that lick." All right. Thank you guys so
much, Mariel.
No, stop. Stop. Stop. Hey, listen. It's
crazy. We got to kill Kanye.
He's got to die. He's got to be dead.
And not like regular kill. Like, we got
to shoot that [__] out of cannon. It's
bad. It's really bad. Do we know what's
going on with Kanye?
this this whole white crowd. No, no, he
made good music or something. What
happened? He's a Nazi now. He's a
hardcore Nazi. He made a song called
High Hitler. So, he's like, "Okay,
you're committed."
And it's bad, man. It's bad. I hate it.
It's obviously It's disgusting. I got to
say that. It's deplorable what he said.
And also, the thing I hate about the
song the most, it's a little bit catchy.
And
we can't have that. It's like in my
head. We can't be having catchy hate
speech, dude.
What if that one song was like, "We link
this [__] on rock and roll." We can't
>> Yeah, that's what this set's going to be
like.
Uh, any clan members in here?
Okay. Heard a woo. I don't like the
clan. So far so good. I will say that
besides the NFL, the KKK is my favorite
white supremacist organization
because like back in the day, man,
people used to commit to racism. You
know, today it's so casual. Everyone's
just doing it. Back in the day, the
clan, they used to make their own robes,
bro. They used to make their own.
Imagine being so racist that you're
like, I'mma learn to sew. You know what
I mean?
You couldn't just go buy those. Those
weren't like the stores at Sheen and
stuff. They weren't mass- prodducing
them in the sweat shops. Honestly, when
you think about it, clan robes were
manufactured more ethically than what
most of us are wearing right now.
Yeah, say what you want about the clan,
but their fashion was sustainable.
The South will rise again. That's
recycling.
I also
I feel like the clan was for dudes who
like wanted to express themselves. They
had no other way to do it, right? Like
were they racist? Yeah. But I also kind
of feel like the clan was for men who
just wanted to dress up. Like I feel
like the clan was for dudes who were too
racist to realize they just wanted to do
drag. Cuz the clan's kind of [__] you
know? It's like I'm a grand dragon. It's
like, yeah, I see you wear magic.
And you know, you put on those robes, if
I wore them, I'd be straight Voggan.
[__] it's giving 1950s lunch counter
cuz you are serving whites only.
I don't know why I was in Milwaukee the
other week doing shows. A lot of people
came up to me and they said, "Sorry for
being white." That did happen. That did
happen. I don't need that. Don't do
that. Cash works fine.
I guess people think I hate white
people. I want to set the record
straight. I don't hate white people.
Okay? Why would you waste your energy
hating a whole group of people who are
already going to hell? It doesn't make
sense.
Don't hate white people. I was adopted
by whites. I was raised by whites.
Sorry, the enemy. Um,
I was raised by white people. Uh, I grew
up in Salt Lake City, Utah, also known
as Mormon Israel.
Yeah, don't laugh. Don't laugh. You're
Hamas if you laugh.
Also, also straight up, let's talk about
it. Israel, like stop, bro. No, but like
stop. You know what I like like like
like like literally like stop it. Like
Israel, you weird.
You we being weird.
Israel's kind of like white women. Oh my
god.
No, no, no. Israel's kind of like white
women because they'll like start
something and then people will be mad.
They'll be like, "I didn't even [__]
do anything. I didn't even do anything.
I didn't really do anything at all. It
was all that and it wasn't me at all.
That's one that I'm going to lose my
career for. Thanks very much.
People are like, "What the fuck?"
I grew up in Salt Lake City. Uh I was
raised Mormon, which is like if you
ordered Christianity on Timu.
Nobody knows what Mormonism is, though.
It's a weird religion. You know, I I
told my friend I was raised Mormon. She
was immediately like, "Oh, so you're not
circumcised?
I got defensive. I was like, "No, [__]
I'm circumcised as hell. I'm I'm mad
circumcised. They They used one of those
crank pencil sharpeners to do my [__]
I wish I wasn't circumcised. That would
be awesome. Then I'd finally have a
place to hide all my rubies."
People know that Mormons were
polygamous. They have multiple wives.
You know, a lot of people had multiple
wives. I'm glad it didn't happen to me
cuz if I got Mormon wives, if I got
Mormon wives, if I got Mormon wives, I
make them fight, bro. I make them fight.
The secret fights of Mormon wives.
That's what we be doing. And if you win
a championship, I'm going to teach you
how to read. That's
So, I grew up with like mostly white
friends, right? Salt Lake City, Utah,
whitest place, mostly white friends. And
they would uh listen to rap music and
they would listen to Eminem who was the
white boy MLK, right?
That's what he was. They're like, "No,
no, no. That's the Reverend Dr. Ms."
And they they would listen to rap and
Eminem, you remember Eminem? He'd be
like, "Here's a gay slur and I hate my
mom." And everybody would be like, "This
is the best rapper ever."
And so they would say [__] to me. They'd
be like, "Yo, like since we be listening
to rap and you got white parents, it's
kind of like we're blacker than you. You
say that." They'd be like, "Oh, we're
like blacker than you." I'd be like,
"All right, well, I hope you get sickle
cell then because
you don't get to say that to me. You
don't get to invalidate my blackness cuz
I got white parents." Like literally
like think about it. I got taken by
white people.
That's like the blackest thing you can
do really.
That's like the original thing of black.
Honestly, the Confederacy would have
lasted longer had they just called it
adoption.
They're like, "What slaves? I got my
house sons and my field sons."
It's like how your job exploits you.
Like here on this plantation, we're a
family.
Thomas Jefferson. Like literally though.
Like literally. Sorry for bringing up
slavery, guys. I grew up drinking a lot
of milk.
full glasses like a [__] zodiac
killer. Like why was I drinking
so much milk? You know what I mean? We
had so much pro milk propag. You
remember those got milk ads? The most
passive aggressive ads of all time.
Those ads that would come on and be
like, "Oh, you don't got milk? What are
you gay?" Like it
Why was I drinking so much milk, bro?
This is crazy. And they said, "You drink
milk, you get strong bones." Do you hear
that growing up? You drink milk, you get
strong bones. That's a lie. That's not
true. I looked it up. I googled it.
Calcium's not real. That's not right.
But you can't lie to me about that.
About food, right? Like what's next? Do
carrots not really help my vision?
Right? Can I digest gum faster than
seven years? Is is cauliflower not doing
ethnic cleansing on broccoli? Like where
do the lies end? I can't handle it. I
become like conspiracy theorist. But
instead of talking about the Illuminati,
I'm always talking about big dairy.
I'm always pulling my friends aside
like, "Why do you think they call it 1%
milk, bro?"
Cuz that's who gets the profits. Think
about it, dog. Now, think about it, D.
Now, think about it. In the American
workforce, what demographic is always
getting paid the least? What demographic
gets paid the least? It's women of
color. Wo. Flip that backwards. What's
that spell? Think about it.
>> All right. I've been Skylie Higgley. You
guys have been phenomenal. Give it up
for yourselves. I'm gonna start my set
with an impression if that's okay.
Actually, I don't care. I'm gonna do it
anyway. So, here it goes.
It's a small world
[Laughter]
after
all.
It's a
[Laughter]
That's me on 1,000 milligrams of Zoloft.
Where are my depressed freaks at? Where
are you? I need a friend. Thank you.
Hello everyone. Uh my name is Sahana J.
Shri Shinbasan. That's a fun long South
Indian name. Um, I accidentally typed in
my name as my bank account password and
it said strong. What?
Didn't even need the numbers or the
dollar sign. Okay.
To no one's surprise, I am uh going
through a breakup currently. Um, it's
been a year.
Um, ladies, do you guys do this? Every
time I go through a breakup, I cut my
hair. Do does anyone I I Yeah, I I cut
my hair. I put it in a box. Send it to
my ex. What?
Yeah, I'm going through a breakup.
Dating's hard. I don't know. Sex is so
weird. I I tried anal recently. That
didn't work. His butthole didn't fit in
my butthole.
Yeah, I did cut my hair. I cut my hair.
It's really short. Something sort of
awful happened. I I posted a video
online and someone commented, "Uhoh,
here comes young Ellen Degenerous.
What?"
I'm like, "Is it cuz I'm white?"
To be fair, the video was me going,
"God, I hate my staff.
I treat him like shit."
Yeah. I don't know. I don't know if I
want to be in a relationship again. Um,
I don't think I can sleep in the same
bed as my partner cuz like where am I
going to put my laundry?
My partner goes in the hamper. Okay.
Laundry goes on the bed. I sleep on the
couch. I don't like car sex. Does anyone
get freaky and have car sex? I don't I
don't like car sex because like when you
have the tinted windows I'm like I can't
even see what you guys are doing in
there.
I'm like, I'm freezing cold out here.
Are you guys going to let me in or
please? No.
Yeah. People don't like having
threesomes with me cuz I'm always like,
"Please, when is it my turn? Can I play?
Can I play?"
I think that sex is like an might
Shyamalan movie cuz like you think it's
going to be good
and then turns out the whole time he was
dead.
Well, you guys haven't seen my dad's
movies.
I'm unemployed. Um,
don't do don't do that. I'm unemployed.
Um, which means my job is basically two
things. Jack off and reply guy. So,
either I'm jacking off or I'm drinking
10 cups of cold brew, logging on to
Instagram, replying to every single one
of my friends Instagram stories going,
"Where is this?
Where is that? Oh, where'd you get that?
Who is that? Hey, are you mad at me? I
love you. Who is that? Wait, wait. Where
is that?
Is anyone replying?" No.
Does that stop me from messaging them
every day? No.
It's my job.
I um I like going to the gym when I'm
not doing that. Um when I'm not jacking
off. I don't I don't like when guys hit
on me when I'm at the gym cuz I'm like,
"Dude, I'm so freaking drunk right now."
I'm like drunk. Hi. I can't even see
you. You know what I mean?
I also like smoking weed. Yeah, I love
that stuff. Um I think I'm the first
person in my family to ever smoke weed.
My Yeah, my parents are both freaking
virgins as hell. So
I I get really um I get really creative
when I smoke weed. I think most
inventions were made when the inventors
were high. Like I think Thomas Edison
was probably like,
"Oh, dude, I get it. I'm just going to
steal my friends ideas."
Where my h my history nerds are over
here. Awesome. That guy was a poser if
you didn't know.
I am bisexual. Hey, you ever seen one
before? West side. Yeah, I am bisexual.
I don't like dating men. They're so
annoying and like they get so grossed
out by stuff. I don't I was talking to
this guy I was seeing about my period
and he got so uncomfortable. It's like
2025. What do you He was like,
"Oh my god, you missed your period."
I was like, "Yeah, dude. Grow up. Raise
my kid."
Can you believe my ex blocked me on
Venmo?
>> Yeah, as if I'm crazy enough to go check
if he blocked me on Venmo. Whatever.
You know what? I actually think we
should go back to oldfashioned
traditional dating. You know, like start
going on dates and then you go steady
and then you get married and then your
husband has disappeared due to
mysterious circumstances.
Was it the poison that you mixed in his
food? Well, oh, I would never do that
now. I
Oh, I'd never put poison in my husband's
food. I I swear I No, it was simply
chicken tikka masala. I swear I
Oh, well, fine. Take me to prison. I
guess that's one place where a man will
let me finish my sentence, you know.
[Applause]
Okay, I'm going to try something. I got
to prove to my parents that I'm um doing
well in my life. Um they're always
asking me stuff like, "Why don't you try
emailing Trevor Noah to get on SNL?" I'm
like, "What are you talking about?"
So, I want to call them during my set if
that's okay.
One time I said I was going to do this
and an audience member was like, "What
time is it over there?" They're in
[__] Texas, bro. What do you
>> Okay, are you ready?
>> Yeah.
>> Hello.
>> Hey, Dad. It's me. What's up?
>> Damn, it's an honor. Are you doing stand
up again?
I am doing standup. Why? What? Why don't
you tell a joke to the audience?
>> I told you to quit years ago, you stupid
[__]
>> Whatever. You got any jokes, Dad?
>> Okay, here's a joke. Your sex life.
>> What the hell? That was like the worst
comeback you've ever said.
I want my come back from your mom.
>> What? Okay, fine. Give the phone to mom
then. Let me talk to mom.
>> Hey, it's mom. An atheist, a rabbi, and
a priest walk into a bar. None of them
want to have sex with you.
>> Wow. What the hell? That's my family,
you guys. They suck.
Okay. Um, I'm going to end on this. If I
ever quit comedy, I would become a
singer. And I want to debut my singing
career tonight if that's okay.
>> And when I'm done, I would love for you
all to laugh. Wait, no. Clap uh
poriously like you've seen the best
freaking thing of your life ever. Are
you guys ready?
>> I'm
going to be doing a cover of the circus
theme song.
[Laughter]
Yeah. D.
[Applause]
Thank you guys so much. I've been Sana.
Thank you.
>> Yes. Keep it going for teachers.
We love teachers. Keep it going for the
firefighters.
Yeah. Make some noise for the troops.
Yeah. Keep it going for the
militaryindustrial complex. Let's hear
it. Make some noise for the innocent
lives lost to abortion.
By which I mean abortion doctors
targeted by prolife activists. Yes.
What?
Keep you on your toes. Keep you guys on
your toes. Hope we're feeling well.
People having drinks. I see. That's
good. Maybe some drugs are happening
here too. Maybe. Do be careful. Be
careful with drugs. I have lost friends
to drugs. By which I mean I did take an
edible and talk too much during Monsters
Inc. So,
did not get invited back to that friend
group. Yeah. Too many hot takes
on Mike and Sully's unique relationship.
But
was in New Orleans last weekend. Any
Nola fans? I I feel like I've been lied
to. No one was telling me this is the
best city. I think the best city in the
US. Like I had so much fun. I had
crawfish atufet which it it to me looked
like sule. So, I imagine this like
dainty pastry. It's actually French for
sludge. It's French for just a pile of
delicious gravy. I had a hurricane, too.
Anybody have a hurricane ever? Came with
a little cherry in it. Isn't it so sexy
when someone can tie a cherry stem with
their tongue? I think that's so sexy.
Like the culture. We just think that's
like the sexiest thing in the world.
When someone can tie tie a cherry stem
with their tongue. I think it's sexy. I
do. Cuz because because because my penis
is the exact shape,
circumference,
and thickness of a cherry stem.
And I can only come when it's tied in a
knot,
which actually blocks the flow of come
leading to what I can only imagine will
one day be the sweet release of orgasm
and death. So I think it's so sexy.
Oh,
the culture.
[Laughter]
I did have fun down there. I uh I am
single. Currently in between [__] at
the moment and I'm trying. Do we have
singles in the room? It's hard. It's
people. The world's not built for us.
It's really scary being single. Not cuz
we'll die alone. We will all die alone.
If you're in a relationship, you're just
kidding yourself. Like it's your path to
take. But being single, you have to live
in constant fear that you're going to
bump into someone at an unexpected
place. You you might meet the one
wherever you go. Like when I go to
Panera, I don't make eye contact with
anyone. That cannot be part of my love
story. I do not. Has anyone been in a
Panera in the past 5 years? What a case
study in the fall of the American
Empire. Like
it is somehow everyone's first day at
the Panera. 18 years old, 80 years old.
They've never touched the POS until I
walk up to them. How do you even find
that many people? You would think you'd
accidentally get someone on their second
day. No, everyone's first day. I think
they're doing severance, but it's
everyone working one day at Panera and
they just we all just don't remember it.
It's embarrassing.
You go in, do you know how rough it is
to know more about the menu than the
person paid to know about the menu? Then
I'm Look, I've worked retail. I know
it's tough, but then suddenly I'm your
first day doula helping you through like
it's okay. No, it's been 20 minutes.
It's not okay. Like the emotional labor
of guiding this prepubescent teen
through his through his first day on the
job. I was in Myrtle Beach and I went
with my mom to Panera. It's like our
little tradition. And this number two of
a pencil behind the register rings up my
entree and then goes, "Oh, this entree
actually comes with a side. your choice
of baguette chips or or or an apple. I
was aware of the stakes, young man.
You're not breaking news to me. Okay.
I've been picking my side since you were
picking which hand to masturbate there,
bud. Okay,
calm down.
And then that they had that lemonade
killing people. That was bad. The Panera
lemonade. It was I don't know which is
worse. Panera hanging over your funeral
as a spectre or Panera playing a role on
your wedding day. So that's why I don't
go. I don't go
keep my eyes to myself. Panera.
The fast casual space is ready for
innovation.
Y'all ever Uber eat and then Uber eat
more?
They say the walk of shame is the
morning after a hookup. The walk of
shame is the 30 steps I took downstairs
to greet the same man
now bringing me cheesecake. It's bad.
Why am I ordering dessert to be brought
to me? Am I a king? Like,
fetch me your finest Brooklyn blackouts.
Like, it's And look, when I get dessert,
I don't want the guy driving across town
for one piece of cake. So, I'll get two
pieces of cake. You know, little meal
prep them for the week ahead. And then,
but then when it gets there, I'm like,
this stuff should not be in the house.
The only way out is through. And then
you
eat it all. The road to rock bottom
paved with innovation. You guys, did you
know you can take an Impossible Whopper
from Burger King, dip it into day old
Papa John's garlic sauce. Oh,
say what you will about latestage
capitalism. The pleasures my tongue has
known.
Our agrarian ancestors never could.
Yeah. The best bite is yet to come.
The end of the world is delicious.
But I'm trying to trying to meet
somebody. I've been experimenting with
bisexuality recently. Yeah. Trump's
going to ban being gay. I'm getting dual
citizenship. So
you can't just flip a switch. I'm
learning. You can't just like suddenly
everybody everybody knows. Like I was
seeing a friend show and one of her
friends was going too. So I was like,
"Oh, I asked her to get dinner before."
And so I messaged her and I read online
when you're straight flirting, you're
supposed to be mean. So I
I was like, "Hey, you want to get
dinner? Wear something cute if you have
anything cute." Got her. Got her good.
Got her real good. Got her real good.
She responds back. She's like, "Oh,
don't have anything cute. Guess I'll
have to wear something slutty." Okay.
Okay. We're playing. We're playing. I
knew what needed to be done. I know what
needed to be done. I'm reading up. I
know what to say.
I went I went, "Good girl.
[Music]
You can vomit in your mouth if you need
to. I was like, "Good girl." Zero to
good girl real quick. Like
we get dinner, nothing happens. I asked
my friend the next day like what the
deal was and she was like, "Oh, I told
her you were a gay man."
So, she was experiencing this very
differently than I was. I wasn't like a
straight guy negging her. I was just a
[__] gay friend. Like,
and my thumb wasn't in her mouth like
good girl. It was like, "Good girl,
where what you want, mama,
the night is yours."
But we did split the check, so
some good can come of it. I'm on the
road a fair amount. I had to visit a
Walgreens recently to purchase personal
lubricant, which um isn't my preferred
place to buy it, but I go in and the
lube is on sale. $16.99 marked down to $
13.99 and I love a deal. So I get to the
register doesn't ring up on sale at
$16.99 but I don't have the strength of
self to to say I know what's going to
happen. I know the know the dance of the
floor manager going to get the lube and
screaming across the crowded Walgreens
like Astro Glides on sale. I just took
the loss. I took the L. And you're not
going to believe me. Y'all aren't going
to believe me. You're like oh he's just
making this up. But seriously, as I was
buying it, a school bus of 100 nuns
comes into the Walgreens and surrounds
it was actually 104 nuns. And you're
going to be like, "How'd you know it was
104?" They had numbers on them. Each of
them had their own little number on them
as they came in. And they didn't come in
order. So, the numbers actually didn't
help me at all. I still had to count
each of them because there were just a
random selection. It was 104 nuns
watching me. So, I was filled with
shame. Next day though, got a little
confidence, a little pep in my step. You
guys know why? because I masturbated.
And I went back went back to the
Walgreens with my receipt to get my $3.
Go up to the register. Lovely lady there
has to walk down to the aisle, get lube
for me, bring it all the way back. I
have to give her my phone number, my
email address, my name, my zip code. I
didn't have a Walgreens account. I
thought 36 years old doesn't have a
Walgreens account. I thought I had a
Walgreens account. And I kid you not,
while I'm getting my $3 back, the same
school bus of 104, you're like, "Oh, we
don't believe it. 104 nuns come circle
me when I get my $3." It's ridiculous.
You don't believe me. You're like, "Oh,
you're just making that up. That's
what's so hard about that fact that it
happened."
You're like, "Why would 104 nuns even go
back to?" So, I lingered after I got my
$3. I stayed. I was in the bushes. I was
like, why are 104 nuns coming back to
the same Walgreens at the exact same
time? I watch from the bushes and each
of them pulls out Astroglide 2.5 O. They
were coming back for their discount,
too. They They were
How many nuns were there?
>> 104.
>> 104. Yeah,
>> cuz it's easy to remember lies.
And that's what Christianity was founded
on.
Applause break.
Calm down. Guys are too good to me.
You're too good to me. Anybody watch
Drag Race?
>> It's a great show. In the finale, Rue
always pulls out an old picture of one
of the queens and has them has them talk
to their younger self. Do you mind?
What's your name, darling?
>> Emma. Emma. I'm pulling out a picture of
8-year-old Emma. Emma, what would you
tell 8-year-old Emma? What would you
say? What would you say to 8-year-old
Emma? What wisdom would you give
8-year-old Emma?
>> What?
>> What
advice would you give to 8-year-old
Emma?
Do I have to answer that? And no,
it would benefit me
and everyone else here if you did,
but I respect your autonomy and
you don't have to.
You can ask a friend.
You can consult. What were you? No
wisdom for a little. Had the you had a
perfect life or
>> Yes. You got your feet on the stage. I
thought you'd be ready to do some
talking.
Are you cute? Chucks. We both got
Chucks. Can we do a Chuck to Chuck?
Yeah. 8-year-old Emma. What are you
going to say to her? Them the person.
I'm sorry.
Consider
your sexuality. What a beautiful what a
beautiful thing to say to your younger
self. I was going to then do this with
another person to establish a pattern
that I would then break with my answer,
but we really spent quite a bit of time
with Emma
[Music]
and so I'm not sure if it's necessary
here. Maybe I'll give you Here's a
picture of 8-year-old Zach. And will you
ask me the same question back?
>> Um, yeah. I consider you sexual.
>> Not not a bad not a bad thing to say.
[Laughter]
Touche, Emma.
I
can't believe you beat me at my own bit.
You know what else I would say to my
younger self?
You know what else I might say to my
I'd tell my younger self. I would tell
my younger self, this isn't going to
work very much cuz we have too much of a
intimate connection. And people, the
visual now is going to be perverse.
I would tell my 8-year-old self not to
masturbate with my mother's conditioner.
[Music]
See what I say? See what now? Because
now every time I hug my mother,
[Music]
just don't do it, young Zach. Don't. You
need to stop or convince her to change
to not the Pantene family of products.
Thank you, Emma. I'm going to get out of
here. Uh before I do, for clips to go
viral, you have to, you know, have a
hook at the beginning of them. something
that catches people's eye online and
makes them stop or whatever. So, I'm
just going to do real quick some hooks.
Make some noise if women are people.
Whoa. Whoa. Took you guys a second.
I'm going to kill myself in the next 60
seconds.
[Applause]
Now, I might.
And let's all have a moment of silence
for the innocent lives lost to abortion.
You guys,
by which I mean abortion doctors
targeted by pro-life activists.
You guys been great. I'm Zach Zin.
>> I love the weather. It's getting warmer,
right? I'm starting to see my neighbors.
You know, in the winter time, I never
see my neighbors. I never see my
neighbors until I am parallel parking.
Then all of New York want to be outside
talking about you got room, you got
space. Keep going. Keep going. Keep
going. Ah, you hit the curb. It's like
where the [__] did you come from? Go
back inside.
What's up, guys? I'm Zubie. I'm a
superstitious person. We got
superstitious people in here.
>> I'm very superstitious, man. I'm I'm I'm
a brown person, okay? So, you know, we
got real crazy superstitions. Okay.
White people, y'all don't have good
superstitions. I'll say that. White
people are just like, "Why would
anything bad happen?"
And you know what? What a way to live. I
love that for you guys. Brown people are
just like, "Only bad things can happen.
Look around, bitch."
Oh man, I grew up with some wild
superstitions, right? Uh the other day
my left eye was twitching. That's bad.
Okay. Left eye twitching. That's bad. I
was like, "Oh my god, he's cheating on
me."
There is no he.
That's just how I felt inside my heart.
Okay. I grew up with some wild
superstition. Like if you bite your
tongue, that means that somebody's
talking [__] about you. You know that?
You bite your tongue, somebody's talking
[__] about you. My family is from
Bangladesh. We know about Bangladesh.
All right. Sick. Y'all been to a Dunkin
Donuts? I love that.
Let me tell you something, okay? I was
so starved for representation as a kid
that I would see a t-shirt that said
made in Bangladesh and I'd be like, "Oh,
we out here, [__]
We made it." Literally, we made the
shirt. Check your tags. All right. Just
[__]
Next time you're Zara, just think of me.
That's all I ask. All right.
Um, and my family's from Bangladesh. And
my my Bengali grandmother would tell me
this one thing growing up in Bangla. She
would say hashi golar pashi which sounds
so cute right even rhymes.
Translated it means if you laugh at
night you choke to death.
This [__] was like some sort of joy
vampire. She was like after sundown
laughter absolutely not. Okay. There are
some good superstitions though. There
are some good ones. Right. Like if your
right hand is itching, that means you're
coming into money. You know this one. If
your right hand is itching, you're
coming into money. Which always works
for me because I steal. So
listen, I see a [__] with a burkin. I'm
like, "Oh, tickle tickle."
What do we have here? Open up.
I'm from New York. Anybody else from New
York in here?
Three people. All right. Just as I
expected. I am from New York, man. I
love being a New Yorker. I love being a
New Yorker. All right. We're tough,
aggressive people. Even Even you guys,
like transplants, you you feel it,
right? You feel the aggression coming in
a little bit violent each year, right?
Like here's an example. I hate cat
callers, right? Cat callers suck. We can
all agree. Boo. Cat callers,
>> right?
But I'm from New York and I have an
attitude problem. So that means I got to
respond.
They're like, "God bless me." I'm like,
"Did I seize?"
Only a woman from New York can be more
intimidating than her predator, right?
They're like, "A ma, let me take you
out." I'm like, "Buy me ice coffee right
now.
What happened? I thought you wanted to
go out."
>> Are you crying right now, you little
[__]
What happened? You little [__]
Why you running? Come back. I am so
lonely.
No, man. Cat calls have gotten weird.
They've gotten weird. They've gotten
personal. Okay. This one time I was
walking down the street minding my
business and this man stops me and he
goes, "You're overthinking it."
First of all, how did you know?
How did you know I was waiting for a
text back from Hector? Like, who told
you?
I do be overthinking it. Okay, I I
overthink when I'm supposed to pull the
thing in the bus. Okay, I'm like, is it
too soon? He just pulled out. Like,
what?
[Music]
I am overthinking it, man.
I think dating culture is over, right?
It's time for the brown people to take
over. We're gonna arrange marry all of
you.
[Applause]
I don't even ask the crowd anymore if
they're dating. Everyone's just like,
"No, we're over that shit."
Uh, dating is tough, man. I'll say that.
Dating's tough. I do think it's a little
easier for women who date men, right? It
It is easy to catch dick. Okay, I'll say
that. It is cuz as a woman, all you have
to do is go anywhere and just say this
phrase. Um,
I didn't understand inception.
And a man will just materialize
out of nowhere. Talking about well
inception is a layered stories about a
dream within a dream within a dream.
Yeah. I'll be a boyfriend and take and I
also want to talk about Batman after
[Applause]
you guys got scared with that one,
didn't you? Yeah.
I did go on a date with a man recently.
I did on a first date. This man goes,
"Zubie, you give me toxic girl vibes."
I was like, "First of all, you're
Dominican. What are you talking about?"
So then I stabbed him. Um, he did ask me
a pretty valid question, right? He was
like, "Would you ever check your
partner's phone?"
Would you guys, anybody here, check your
partner's phone?
Silence.
Everyone here is healed.
love that for you. Well, I said no. I
was like, "Ew, y'all take your phones to
the bathroom. That's nasty."
Okay, I'm not trying to get like finger
herpes or whatever.
I was like, "Listen, if there was
something I needed to find out, the
truth will eventually come to light,
right? The truth will eventually come to
light or
I'll make something up in my head."
He was right about the toxic thing.
Cuz here's the thing, guys. Why would I
need to check your phone if the truth
came to me in a dream last night? You
know what I'm saying? Like I don't
I got premonition for days, [__]
I don't need you.
[Laughter]
Uh I'm in my 30s. I'm in my 30s. Anybody
else in their 30s? Make some noise.
Okay, that was one sexy yawn. Hell yeah.
No, I love I love my 30s, man. I like my
30s. You really know who you are in your
30s, right? You're like, "Man, I can
wear one type of sock." Okay,
I'm a Hannes [__] till I die now. You
know what I'm saying? Like, you don't
[__] with other things. You're just This
is who you are now. You know, spending
way too much time in the bread aisle
trying to figure out what's giving you
gas. You're like, is it riboflavaughing?
Show yourself.
I do. I I like my 30s. It is a little
bit embarrassing dating in your 30s,
though. You know, it is because as a
millennial, I'm just like, how am I
supposed to have a crush when I barely
have the will to live? You know, like I
just
personally I can't do it anymore.
Uh I have friends in their 30s coming up
to me being like, "Zubie, I have a
crush." I'm like, "Bitch, you should
have a family." Okay.
The [__] is going on, man? We got to
stop with this. Get out of that polycle.
Okay. We It's over. It's over. Stop
trying to be sexy. It's It's done. Okay.
Oh man. We know about polyamory.
Polyamory polycules.
No. There should be some of you in one
right now. Okay. Polyamory is just micro
doing a cult. You know,
it is. There's no reason to be scared.
Or just another thing that white women
in Brooklyn stole from Muslims. Okay.
Four wives. That was already a Come on.
That was us. I'm kidding. I know it's
not the same thing. But I did I did meet
a couple one time in a polycule and I
asked them how many people were in their
polycule. They said 10 people.
10 people. I was like, "Bitch, that is a
startup." Okay,
you better get your LLC right now. Okay.
Sign some tax forms. What are you doing?
All right, matter of fact, call HR. Some
of you are not clocking in. Okay, I
don't know if you guys know how
Polycules work, but they are keeping
charts. Okay, they're keeping charts.
They're on Google Suite. Okay, they're
paying for the whole thing. All right,
you ever made a chart for the love of
your life? All right, they're making
pivot tables to figure out who's going
on a date with who.
I'm just like, [__] [__] cheat on
me. Okay, just cheat like a normal lie.
lie like a normal person. I'll figure it
out. My eye will twitch. Like I don't
You guys having so much fun. Keep it
going for your
>> I'm 42. Uh
well, that's so funny. You can be 42 in
Brooklyn. They'll let you do it.
They let you be 38. They'll let you do
the whole thing. Um and I am thinking
about more mortality a lot more. I just
I never been this close to dropping
dead. That's why I I'm dressing better.
I cut out graphic TE's. I can't be found
in a band shirt.
Some poor paramedics like white male
40s. Billy Joel, River of Dreams tour.
Guess he had a heart attack.
[Laughter]
But yeah, I'm at an age too where like
everyone's pressing me to have kids. Uh,
I never really been into it, but uh, I
am a first- time uncle. I got a
three-year-old niece named Annabelle.
She's kind of turned the tide. I've seen
the perks cuz I always feel so dumb, you
know? I've been alive so long. I know so
little. I hang out with her, she knows
nothing. I feel like a genius. It's
incredible. We walk around, she'll be
like, "Auntie, what that?" I'm like, "A
bucket?" She's like, "Bucket."
And I'm like, "I am a smart man." Uh,
but then I realized my own life. My best
friend is a physics teacher. His wife is
an electrical engineer. I was like, "Oh,
I'm his Annabelle."
All day. I'm like, "What the?" He's
like, "That's why Earth can't be heated
by moonlight." I'm like, "Fuck it."
Oh,
but then toddlers, they decimate your
self worth, too. They love to humiliate
you with the games they make you play.
My niece, her favorite game is called
Baby. She's the mom. I'm the baby. And
she puts on this terrifying little
voice. Like her whole demeanor changes.
She just walks up to me and she just
goes, "What's wrong, baby?"
[Music]
And I have to be like, "I'm sad."
She's like, "That's good, baby."
And then she makes me weep. She's like a
director who needs options. She's She's
like, "Now, cry, baby. Why?"
And I have to be like
in front of my in-laws, mind you, who no
longer respect me.
I can feel my wife being like, "I'll
never [__] you again." Like, those days
are long gone for you.
And then the whole game ends. She goes,
"Does baby need his bottle?" And then
she force-feeds me from a fake plastic
bottle. And then she goes, "Dare there.
Now the baby feel better.
Like no, the baby feel unsettled. Who
are you? But I guess it is an applicable
skill cuz people the kids are always
like what do you think she's going to
grow up to be? I'm like dominatrix. Uh
seems like that is the route.
But then parents too, man. You love your
kids so much you lose sight of reality.
I got a one-year-old nephew too and he
loves Minnie Mouse. I was in Target. I
saw a Minnie Mouse shirt. I just want to
get him the shirt. I asked my
sister-in-law. She goes, "No, Minnie.
Only Mickey. I'm concerned about his
masculinity."
>> Oh my god.
>> I know, man. Yeah. He drinks milk out of
a sippy cup. Like, I don't think
anyone's going to be like, "Do we have
an alpha in the room?" Like, are you
Ryan?
>> It's not homophobia either. Like,
obviously, she knows liking Minnie Mouse
is not going to change his sexuality.
That is how far we have come. She's
like, "If he's gay, he's gay, but no son
of mine, Bottoms.
[Laughter]
But anyway,
I did not get him the shirt. I got him a
wife beater
that says [__] slaps.
It'll be fine. We are thinking about
having kids. And I get it. You know the
dilemma of doing that now, especially
with climate change. Everybody that I
tell that to, they're like, "It is
irresponsible bringing a child into this
world." It's like, man, shut up. You
don't know my child. Maybe they'd thrive
in that landscape.
Some little machete warlord I can't
control.
Other parents were like, "My kid got
straight A's." I'm like, "Frederick is
siphoning gas at a fourth grade level.
Nobody sucks like my boy." Even if we
are wiped out as a species, it's not
going to matter. whoever we were, our
best people, their accomplishments. Look
at the dinosaurs. They just have whoever
representing their existence. Just
follow me. Uh,
they ruled the earth. They died out. We
dug up their bones with We don't even
know if these were famous dinosaurs.
Just some mediocre raptor who died at
the right time in the Smithsonian. The
other dinosaurs are probably like, "You
put up Charles. We used to make fun of
his hands."
My point is
we will be the dinosaurs to whoever
inherits the earth next. They're going
to dig up barb bones, put them in their
museums. It's not going to be Michael
Jordan. Depending where you look, it's
going to be whatever group there was the
most of us. America, we got real estate
agents slash entrepreneurs.
Europe, they got soccer players with
floppy hair.
China, they fair and just leaders. uh
who care about their citizens so much.
They watch their every move. Good
people. I think
I will say the one group we do have in
abundance and this is a [__] up
thought, but uh great artists,
musicians, even comedians who have
turned out to be pedophiles.
With that in mind, do you think regular
pedophiles are like, "Do I have a hidden
talent?
And
do you think regular pedophiles think
they're better than celebrity
pedophiles? They're like, "Yeah, anyone
could lure a kid with a private plane.
I'm doing this on a teacher salary.
Those are chops." As far as I know,
I'll unite the room. I'll tell you what
I like about gay guys.
I'm straight, but they're better than
us. Wherever they go, they make
everywhere so much more aesthetically
pleasing. I think it's cuz hygienically,
there's nothing dirtier than a man's
[__]
So,
for them to do what they love to do with
an [__] they have to meticulously
clean and scrub their own. And if you
can turn a butthole into a vagina, you
can make a house into a home.
I don't know. I I mean, I've I've lived
in New York for 15 years. Obviously,
it's a very woke town. Uh some ways it
has made me more conservative cuz like,
you know, we aren't thinking about
having kids and then, you know, I'm
pretty liberal guy. And then someone
will be like, "Bin Laden was
misunderstood." I'm like, "Yeah, I'll
homeschool my kids." Uh I don't really
care about that.
But it definitely made me more
progressive. It's definitely helped me
understand being trans.
could
a lot of what being trans is is you're
sacrificing what might have been an
easier life to be exactly who you are.
That's everybody who lives here.
They're like, "Yeah, I could have been a
homeowner in Portland, Maine. Now I
split a two-bedroom with four people cuz
I got to be me."
But no, I am trying to have more uh
empathy in general. Like I feel bad for
Gen Z. I know they're having less sex
because porn to sensitize them. That's
definitely true. Before porn, man, to
turn me on, I just had to be near a bra,
man. Now I'm so jaded. I've watched
videos where after the scene ends, the
actors come back on just to let you know
they're okay.
[Music]
Like they do with animals in movies. Uh
they're like, "No one's hurt during the
taping of Schindler's Fist. Everyone's
fine." You guys are great, man. Thanks
so much. Have a good rest. Bye-bye.
[Music]